phuket.net 2014-06-29

# Privacy - Phuket.Net

## Overview

At Phuket.Net, we understand and respect the importance of your privacy. It is our policy that personal information, such as your name, postal address, e-mail address or telephone number is **private and confidential**.

Accordingly, the personal information you provide is accessible only by designated staff and is only used for the purpose for which you provide the information, (such as pay for advertising or to book a hotel room). 

**Personal information is not released to third parties** , except if release is required by law, or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings. There are no other circumstances under which we will provide or sell personal information to third parties.

## Cookies

A “cookie” is a small message given to your web browser by our web server. The browser stores the message in a text file, and the message is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Phuket.net may make use of cookies on our website for the purposes of tailoring our web pages to your needs. We do not use cookies to track your movements after leaving this website. 

Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies, and the help menu on your browser should tell you how. However, switching off cookies could restrict your use of our website. 

## Newsletters and Correspondence

Phuket.Net may use the information you provide us to send you newsletters, email, or other communications that you may find of use, such as promotions or information about upcoming events. All of these communications will include instructions explaining how you can request that we not send you (“opt out” of) future communications of the same type. 

## Website Statistics and Usage Profile

We analyse our website log files and general statistics and make this in part available to third parties such as advertisers. This does not include any personal information and is general data such as number of visitors, pages accessed, country of origin, number of goods and services purchased, etc. 

In order to display advertisements on third party websites such as Google, Yahoo and Bing we use cookies to serve ads and to monitor which ads drive visitors to our site, as well as those of our affiliates and partners. Should you wish to opt out of the use of cookies by third parties please visit the opt out page on the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) website.

## Links to Other Sites

Phuket.Net contains content, services, advertising and other materials that link to web sites operated by other parties. We have no control over those other sites, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to them.
